there are only three days left in this
election while we hope the Donald will
become the president and he works hard
everyday for your support we need you
the voters to go out vote and make that
a reality we also ask that you bring
your family friends neighbors to vote
for President Donald Trump
why should you vote for Donald because
we need a president who will keep us
safe
we need a president who will secure the
border we need a president who will
break up the corruption and collusion in
our government we need a president who
will bring jobs back to America we need
a president who will lower taxes and
they're energized the economy we need a
president who will not leave any
Americans behind we need a president who
will put America first domestically and
abroad we need a president who will
deliver the change you all have been
waiting for this is your last chance
your last chance to make a real
difference
ladies and gentlemen please say hello to
my husband and the future President of
the United States of America Donald
Trump
so folks I'm going to were see you guys
in a little while but what am I going to
do what do i have to say i'm going to
leave goodbye but I'm gonna want a great
job
what a great job and that's five
languages right that's not easy to do I
couldn't do it
that's really amazing thank you honey
and i have my boy Eric and his great
wife Laura who comes from this area
right right alongside haha and we have a
very very powerful man who here is doing
very well
is it working out well come here
governor
he's been loyal to trump from day one we
needed outsider to clean up washington
DC just like we have an outsider to
clean up raleigh north carolina this is
the best of America god bless you all
thank you very much
he's a fantastic guy he's been there
from day one to believe me so I just
want to thank everybody for being here
it's a an amazing situation that we're
going through but i can tell you we are
going to win and we're gonna win big
Hillary Clinton is all of these
celebrities and failed politicians out
campaigning for her and she has crowd so
much smaller than ours i just have me
but I have my family I have my family
I've had Erik and Laura and don don jr
and ivanka nobody's ever heard of a vaca
and Tiffany every one of them now Baron
somedays a little young but i will tell
you I've had my family they've been all
over and Mike Pence has been incredible
to buy the world
I'll tell you he's been incredible in
three days we are going to win the great
state of North Carolina and we are going
to win back the White House real change
begins with immediately immediately
repealing and replacing Obamacare it's
just been announced that the residents
of North Carolina are going to
experience massive double-digit premium
hikes so high and I say this to all the
groups because it's also hired certain
pressing I don't want to tell him what
it is so i won't tell you because right
now you're happy and you'd be very said
you probably turn your head down and
start leaving but it's bad in the great
state of Arizona as an example premiums
are going up more than one hundred and
sixteen percent 95 of 100 north carolina
counties will only have one insurer in
the obamacare exchange next year lots of
luck with that negotiation premiums is
searching companies are leaving insurers
are fleeing doctors are quitting and
deductibles are going through the roof
yet Hillary Clinton wants to double down
and Obamacare making it even more
expensive and in fact much more
expensive i'm asking you for your vote
so we can repeal and replace Obamacare
and save healthcare not only for North
Carolina but for the country some s real
change also means restoring honesty to
government as you know the FBI has
reopened its criminal investigation of
Hillary
they're also conducting a second
criminal investigation into Hillary's
pay-for-play corruption at the State
Department it has just been confirmed
that the 650,000 emails they discovered
that weren't turned in by the way they
discovered them thank you to mr. Anthony
Weiner include brand new emails not
previously turned over to authorities
likely including even more classified
information and may be classified at the
highest highest level how said however
the reports also show that the political
leadership at the Department of Justice
is trying very hard as hard as they can
to protect Hillary Clinton
think of it I think of it you have a
great four star general that right now
current a current four-star general that
right now
general Cartwright james Cartwright is
possibly going to be serving as much as
five years in jail
General Petraeus great general his life
was destroyed young man took some
pictures of a submarine he's in jail now
for a year I watched his mother the
other night and Hillary Clinton's
running for president and she's done 25
times worse than any of them or all of
them put together John Podesta her boss
her head said that she has bad instincts
pretty bad when your person your top
person working for you said you have bad
instincts that came out on Wikileaks
Bernie Sanders would say constantly
during the debates which by the way she
received the questions nobody ever says
anything about can you imagine if i
received the questions to the debates
they would call for my immediate
withdrawal you don't even hear about it
from you don't even hear about it but
Bernie Sanders said she's bad bad
judgment she does just take a look at
what she's done
take a look at the email mess how about
if she's running the country can't even
run an email
Hillary created an illegal email server
to shield their criminal activity and
then she illegally destroyed 33,000
emails after receiving a congressional
subpoena
I mean think of that she made 13 phones
disappear somewhere the hammer
she is the most corrupt person ever to
seek the office of the presidency
if she were to win it would create an
unprecedented constitutional crisis if
she ever got into the Oval Office
Hillary under special interest would rob
this country blind you've seen what's
happened
the Clinton family have made themselves
rich by being in politics as President
Harry Truman once said you can't get
rich in politics unless you're a crook
which is an interesting seventh harry
truman my contract with the American
voter begins with a plan to end
government corruption and to take our
country back from the special interests
and you know I used to be on the other
side of things in case you didn't know
and I let a very nice life but i also
love our country and this was an easy
decision i went from being the ultimate
insider to being an outsider like
they've never seen before we are doing
so well this is a movement like that
never ever seen before
it never seen anything like this before
i love this country
I want the entire corrupt Washington
establishment to hear the words we all
are about to see when we win a november
eight we are going to Washington and we
will drain la soie cultural so true an
expression I've gotten to like at the
core of my contract is my plan to bring
back our jobs
North Carolina has lost nearly half of
its manufacturing job since NAFTA a deal
signed by bill clinton and supported by
crooked Hillary Clinton America is lost
70,000 factory since China entered the
World Trade Organization another bill
and hillary back disaster
we're living through the greatest jobs
theft in the history
any of the world nobody has ever taken
jobs from anyone like other countries
have taken our jobs
thank you i love you too rough guy he's
a rough sounding guy but i do love him I
do love him I love you all
I guess that's why I'm doing this I
guess right I guess pillow tex laid off
1125 workers and move their jobs to
Mexico and other countries freightliner
later 500 workers in mount holly and
move their jobs to Mexico brunswick
corporation laid off 212 workers and
move their jobs to Mexico flextronics
I'm not gonna buy their product anymore
laid off 312 work in charlotte and move
their jobs to Mexico China and various
other countries and many many more we
could go on all day long with that a
trump administration will stop the jobs
from leaving America and we will stop
the jobs from leaving North Carolina
that i can tell you the theft of
American prosperity will end and it will
end immediately upon taking office if a
company wants to fire their workers
leave North Carolina moved to another
country and then ship their products
back into the United States we will make
them pay a tax of thirty-five percent
and I'll tell you what's gonna happen
they're not leaving they're not gonna
leave and for the ones that do that's
okay we'll make a fortune when they sell
their products into the schedule but
they won't be leaving North Carolina it
in so quickly now the politicians
probably knew this i'm sure you've never
heard it before
probably have it but you'll stop it
immediately the outflow of jobs from our
country is disgraceful to disgrace a
trump administration will renegotiate
NAFTA and if we don't get the deal we
want we will terminate NAFTA and get a
much better deal for our companies and
our workers we will also immediately
stop the job-killing trans-pacific
partnership with Hillary Clinton loved
and said it's the gold standard it is
the gold standard for other countries
not for us
that'll take the rest of our jobs as
part of our plan to bring back jobs we
are going to show and create lower taxes
on American business from thirty-five
percent down to fifteen percent it will
start the engine running like you've
never seen
we will massively cut taxes for the
middle class and hillary wants to
increase your taxes by a lot so between
Obamacare which will double and double
and double and higher taxes you're not
going to be happy if you have Hillary
Clinton we will unleash the American
energy and i'll tell you we have such
power right under our feet including
shale oil natural gas and clean coal
going to put our miners back to work
we're going to put our steel workers
back to work our plan will end the EPA
intrusion into your family farms stop
the double taxation of family farms at
that
we will stop that their farms the father
dies they have to sell their farm to pay
the taxes that's going to end we will
cancel billions of dollars in global
warming payments to the United Nations
nobody knows where that money go and use
that money to invest in America
including roads ports bridges waterways
will build highways will fix our
existing roads will fix our bridges half
of which are in horrible condition some
of which are in dangerous condition we
will rebuild our infrastructure and will
rebuild our inner cities the
african-american community the Hispanic
community living in the inner cities
treated so unfairly high-crime bad
education no jobs we will fix it we will
fix it
believe me and we will fix it quickly
the Democrats for a hundred years
they've run the inner cities and all
they do is every four years they come
around give me a vote give me a vote you
given the vote they see in four years
they do nothing
we will fix the inner cities will bring
back jobs will bring back safety we will
bring back education all i say is this
what the hell do you have to lose
I will fix it give us a chance
believe me been very unfair been very
unfair to the african-american community
Hispanic communities give us a chance we
will fix it we will become a rich nation
once again but to be rich nation we must
also be a safe nation hillary wants a
550 present increase in Syrian refugees
pouring into our country
her plan will import generations of
terrorism extremism and radicalism into
you schools and into your communities
all throughout when I'm elected
president we will suspend the Syrian
refugee program and we will keep radical
Islamic errands the hell out of our
country have no choice we have no choice
and we all have a heart and will build
safe zones in Syria will get the Gulf
states to pay for because we are 20
trillion dollars we don't need to pay
anymore
we have to fix our own country but will
help them and we'll get people that
frankly have plenty of money to pay and
they'll be happy to do it
a trump administration will also secure
defend the borders of the United States
and yes we will build a great wall
we've received the first-ever
endorsement issued by America's
incredible people the border patrol
officers and ice never given an
endorsement before it's just been
reported that as a result of our open
borders violent cartels have spread into
all 50 of our state's more than ninety
percent of those arrested are illegal
they're here illegally think of it
ninety percent are here illegally you
ask yourself what are we doing what are
we doing
they're killing innocent America's
threatening and they are just killing
innocent Americans take a look at what's
happening threatening schools and
destroying communities a government that
will not protect its people is a
government that is unworthy to lead and
unworthy to serve as Secretary of State
Hillary Clinton allowed thousands of the
most dangerous and violent criminal
aliens to go free because their home
countries were very smart they wouldn't
take him back we bring them there they
say get out of here
murderers drug lords gang heads would
bring their they say we don't want him
back
we don't want him back well let me tell
you something
there won't be one instance in four
years or eight years where we bring them
into their country that they come back
and our country that I can promise they
came back all the time they said we
don't want them and she would say oh
that's okay bring him back put them
right out on the streets and you know
what's happened
Hillary Clinton supports totally open
borders there goes your country and
support sanctuary cities like in san
francisco where Kate Steinle was
murdered by an illegal immigrant
deported at least five times thousands
of Americans would be alive today if it
were not for the open border policy of
obama and clinton here in North Carolina
20-year old Liana Noma and a run born
child were killed by an illegal
immigrant with two prior deportation
leanna's killer had two prior DUI
convictions for driving with a revoked
license and a conviction for assault
charges very serious assault and people
that knew him back to have him
incarcerated or deported but they
wouldn't do it another amazing American
lost his life to illegal immigration was
John Wilkinson whose mother I've gotten
to know during the campaign Josh a
student in high school was murdered at
the age of 17 credible young man great
student great person everybody loved him
he was tortured strangled and beaten to
death by an illegal immigrant and then
his body was set on fire everybody said
please incarcerate this maniac they
wouldn't do it a trump administration
will end this nightmare of violence we
will protect American lives we will
cancel all federal funding to sanctuary
cities we will stop illegal immigration
deport every last criminal Alien and
dismantle every criminal gang in cartel
threatening our citizens and that'll
happen very quickly when we win you will
finally have a government on your side
fighting your community and protecting
your family
we will also repeal the obama-clinton
defense requests and rebuild our badly
depleted military we have great people
we have great great people North
Carolina will be at the very center of
this effort with new advanced fighters
flying from seymour johnson air force
base we will have the newest and the
best not the old stuff that's 18 and 20
years old where they don't even make
parts anymore
we will have the newest and the best and
marine battalions at Camp Lejeune I know
camp lejeune will we're going to be
increasing the numbers and did we ever
need it more yeah there were times when
we needed it badly but we're right at
the top right now we need our great
military and have major new investments
also made to Fort Bragg anybody from
Fort Bragg so we were there the other
night
we're 23,000 people it was an admit was
anybody there that was an amazing
evening
that was an incredible evening we had
generals we had Admirals we had
recipients of the medal of honor that
was an incredible evening and some of
the people who have given us the
endorsement we have over 200 Admirals
and Generals we have 22 medal of honor
recipients who have totally endorse me
the numbers increasing on a daily basis
they like our thought process they like
when we go into Mosul that we do it
quietly that we don't announce it for
months in advance
we're going into Mosul in four months
why do they have to say that why do they
have to say that and you see the
resistance is now very said we're going
in because we think Isis leaders are
staying there and we are going to get
them three months
we're going into Mosul two months we're
going into months one month one week
well let me tell you they left the first
time they heard it they were gone and
it's being very very tough human shields
are being used all sorts of booby traps
are being set
why can't we go with surprise right
member and I mean in high school it's
called the element of surprise
General Douglas MacArthur general george
patton can you imagine what they would
be thinking if they saw this stupidity
this stupidity of our leadership and we
have a leader only does his campaigns
for cooking I mean all he's doing is
campaigning for crooked Hillary that's
only wants to do and you know she can't
get any crowds and she doesn't have what
it takes to do rallies all over the
place she wants to go home and go to
sleep so she's got Biden he challenged
me he challenged me
oh I'd like to take him i'd like to take
him behind the gym are i dream of that I
dream
let me just tell you hey folks let me
just tell you if I ever said that if I
ever said that they thought it was so
cute all was that wonderful what our
vice president said if I ever said that
all he's a bully he's a horrible person
he challenged our Vice President to a
fight
can you imagine what a bully he is much
smarter much better education much
everything I mean give me a break
they have Biden going around they have
all these people and then when they
can't when that doesn't work because you
know Obama is going wherever I go I see
Air Force One and who's paying for Air
Force One
there as he travels to campaign but
wherever I go and I see him screaming at
people that are protesters and with me
they show the protester with him they
just kept the camera they didn't want to
show the protest but i'll tell you what
he should not be campaigning for Hillary
Clinton he should be in the oval office
working on jobs working on building up
our military working on good trade deals
and you know the press which is the
world's most dishonest people these
people they never show these Krauts they
never show the crowds never ever they
never show the crowds but you know the
press and I must tell you one of the
things I've learned is the press is I
mean honestly they're among the most
dishonest people I've ever met in my
life
they're bad people they're bad people
and the other thing I've learned is how
great the people of the united states
are their incredible purple their
incredible people but the press is very
concerned because the polls are so good
by the way the last fall i hate to say
we're winning North Carolina
we're winning in Ohio we're winning in
New Hampshire we're winning in Iowa
we're winning in Florida we're winning
all over the place they're going crazy
one of the people yesterday said oh
goodness look at this supposed to be a
you know non-biased a report came in on
New Hampshire where up we're winning
we're winning everywhere but a report
came in New Hampshire says we're winning
and the person goes oh gosh oh look look
at this
we're winning almost everywhere folks
this is going to be brexit this is going
to be special you have to get out and
vote but this is going to be special
we're going to bring our jobs back we're
going to take care of our incredible
veterans who have been mistreated so
badly
we're gonna build up our military we're
going to do so many things Hillary
Clinton brought death and disaster to
Iraq and Syria and Libya she empowered
Iran and she Unleashed Isis across the
world by creating the vacuum there was
no Isis when she was Secretary of State
at the beginning she Unleashed Isis and
at the debates
by the way did i win the debate those
debates but I was a little concerned
because she kept sayin for like a week
and a half
she's in debate prep I kept saying what
am i doing that you know I don't mind
the big prep but you supposed to know
this stuff you're not supposed to be
prepping too much she was in debate prep
every time for a week to a week and a
half and and by the way every single
online paul said i won the debates by
many as one had 9210 but that we won the
debates but she's prepping but she
wasn't really prepping she was actually
resting and sleeping folks this is not
what you need for your president with
China ripping us off on tread and we're
gonna have a great relationship with
China with Japan with all of these
countries what they're doing to us is
incredible incredible Mexico at the
border mexico with trade we have a
massive
trade deficit with mexico worldwide we
have almost and 800 billion dollar trade
deficit think of it you say who's our
negotiators we have the greatest
business people in the world the
greatest negotiators in the world we use
political hacks Hillary in our failed
establishment have spent six trillion
dollars on wars in the Middle East that
we never win and now the Middle East is
in worse shape Farley I mean there's not
even a contest than ever before worship
than ever before they dragged us into
foreign wars that make us less safe
shipped our goods and wealth to other
countries and they left our borders wide
open at home we send our troops to
foreign countries to defend their
borders but our politicians refuse to
defend our borders that will change in
november eight and Trump administration
will never ever put the interests of a
foreign country before the interests of
our country from now on it will be
America first
two all-americans I say it's time for
change it's time for new leadership can
you imagine four more years of Obama
meaning high taxes think of it high
taxes Isis all over the place
radical Islamic terrorists all thing she
will be worse than Obama she will be
worse that obama just think about what
we can accomplish in the first 100 days
of a trump administration we're going to
have the biggest tax cut since Ronald
Reagan even bigger she's gonna raise
your taxes we will eliminate every
unnecessary job-killing regulation can
so every illegal Obama executive order
we will protect religious liberty have
to do rebuild our military and take
great great care of our phenomenal
veterans we will provide school choice
and put it into common core were
bringing our education local we will
support the great men and women of law
enforcement
we're going to save the Second Amendment
which is under siege and appoint
justices to the United States Supreme
Court who will uphold and defend the
Constitution of the United States it's
time to cut our ties with the failed
politicians of the past
Hillary Clinton is a candidate of
yesterday we are the movement of the
future we are the movement of the future
and it's such a beautiful sight look I'm
looking all the way over to that hangar
over there the people are lined up that
is a lot of people man
it's always a lot of people all the way
to the back of this
hello folks it's an amazing thing and
this is taking place all over the
country no matter where we go
whether it's a hanger whether it's
Hershey Pennsylvania where the most
incredible crowd you've ever seen
I mean just everyday everynight the
crowds are incredible
we're fighting for every parent who lost
their child to drugs and crime and gang
violence
we're fighting for every community whose
jobs and dreams have been ripped out and
shipped to other countries
we're fighting for every American who
believes government should serve the
people not the donors and not the
special interest i'm asking you to dream
big because with your vote we are just
three days away from the change you've
been waiting for for your entire life
so I want to thank all of the people who
supported me I want to thank my
incredible incredible family I want to
thank your incredible governor get out
and vote for Fox is a good man and he's
going to do a great job but we are going
to all get together we're going to those
Falls together we will make America
wealthy again we will make America
strong again we will make America safe
again and we will make America great
again thank you very much everybody
thank you thank you very much
fantastic people god bless you everybody